let quiz=[
    {
        question:"How many months make a Century?",
        option:[
            "12", 
            "120", 
            "1200", 
            "12000", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Whon is the Father of Cryptology?",
        option:[
            "Leon Battista", 
            "Giuseppe Peano", 
            "Arnold Sommerfeld", 
            "Willam Oughtred", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Where did the 'Magic Square originate'?",
        option:[
            "Ancient China", 
            "Ancient Nepal", 
            "Ancient India", 
            "Ancient Japan", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the 'Father of Mathematics?",
        option:[
            "Giuseppe Peano", 
            "Ramanujam", 
            "Archimedes", 
            "Aryabhatta", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:" Find the missing number in the series 5, 10, 17, _, 37, 50, 65, 82?",
        option:[
            "26", 
            "21", 
            "28", 
            "23", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which number does not have a Reciprocal? ",
        option:[
            "-1", 
            "0", 
            "1", 
            "None of these", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"If one number is thrice the other and their sum is 24, then the numbers are _________.",
        option:[
            "4,12", 
            "6,15", 
            "3,9", 
            "None of these", 
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"A clock strikes once at 1 o’clock, twice at 2 o’clock, thrice at 3 o’clock and so on. How many times will it strike in 24 hours?",
        option:[
            "78", 
            "136", 
            "156", 
            "196", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:" Calculate the Rate of Interest for a certain sum of money that becomes 5 times its principal Amount in 10 years? ",
        option:[
            "40%", 
            "30%", 
            "20%", 
            "10%", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the average of first 50 natural numbers?",
        option:[
            "25.30", 
            "25.0", 
            "25.5", 
            "12.25", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
] ;

